{"data":[{"question":"The dog is getting old and can not run _________ it did.","a":"so fast than","b":"as faster as","c":"as fast as","d":"so faster as","answer":"3","explain":"- As + adverb+ as","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Amy plays volleyball _________, if not better than, Joy.","a":"as well as","b":"as well","c":"so well as","d":"so well","answer":"1","explain":"- as + adverb+ as: the comparison of equality","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"It is generally believed that teaching is ___ it is a science.","a":"much an art as","b":"an art much as","c":"as much an art as","d":"as an art much as","answer":"3","explain":"- As + much + single noun + as","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"After the new technology was introduced, the company produced ___ books in 2006 as the year before.","a":"as many twice","b":"as twice many","c":"twice many as","d":"twice as many","answer":"4","explain":"- We use the comparison of equality: twice\/three times + as + adjective\/adverb + as","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"How did you find your visit to the amusement park? \"I thoroughly enjoyed it. It was ___ than I expected.\"","a":"even much exciting","b":"far more exciting","c":"a lot much exciting","d":"so more exciting","answer":"2","explain":"- far + comparative form","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Which is _________ country, Germany or France?","a":"the larger","b":"a large","c":"larger","d":"a larger","answer":"1","explain":"- We use \"the\" because Germany and France are clear in this situation. (see a, an the)\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If you don't like the blue coat, take the red one. \"OK, but do you have ___ size in blue? This one's a bit loose for me.\"","a":"a smaller","b":"a small","c":"the smaller","d":"the small","answer":"1","explain":"- a + adj + noun\n ( see a, an, the)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"If there were no examinations, students should have ___ at school.","a":"a more happier time","b":"the happiest time","c":"a much happier time","d":"much happiest time","answer":"3","explain":"- much + comparative form","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"How beautifully that lady sings! I have never heard ___.","a":"a good voice","b":"the better voice","c":"a better voice","d":"the best voice","answer":"3","explain":"- I have never heard a better voice: means she is the best singer","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Which do you think tastes ___, the beef or the pork?","a":"good","b":"well","c":"best","d":"better","answer":"4","explain":"- tastes better (compare between the beef and the pork)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}